https://www.spacesaver.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy PolicySpacesaver » Privacy Policy
This policy was last updated July 2017.
Spacesaver Corporation (“Spacesaver”, “us” or “we”) is committed to protecting the privacy of your personal information. To that end, no information collected through this website will be sold, disclosed, distributed, or otherwise made available to third parties, other than as described below or with your prior approval.
COLLECTING PERSONAL INFORMATION
Spacesaver collects certain information from users of this site. This information includes, but is not limited to, IP addresses, referring IP addresses (i.e., search engines used to find this site), data on the pages viewed, site traveled to if the user exits this site using the Sales Office Locator, and the last page viewed on this site.
As you browse Spacesaver.com  advertising cookies will be placed on your computer so that we can understand what you are interested in. Our display advertising partner, AdRoll, then enables us to present you with retargeting advertising on other sites based on your previous interaction with Spacesaver.com. The techniques our partners employ do not collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address, or telephone number.  You can visit this page to opt out of AdRoll’s and their partners’ targeted advertising.
In order to better enable you to determine whether you wish to opt out of cookies, here is a list of cookies we use:
_session_id, unique token, sessional, Allows Shopify to store information about your session (referrer, landing page, etc).
_shopify_visit, no data held, Persistent for 30 minutes from the last visit, Used by our website provider’s internal stats tracker to record the number of visits
_shopify_uniq, no data held, expires midnight (relative to the visitor) of the next day, Counts the number of visits to a store by a single customer.
cart, unique token, persistent for 2 weeks, Stores information about the contents of your cart.
_secure_session_id, unique token, sessional
storefront_digest, unique token, indefinite If the shop has a password, this is used to determine if the current visitor has access.
Spacesaver also provides potential customers the opportunity to contact us via the “Download” or “Contact Us” form. Users freely provide Spacesaver with product requests and other information through these forms. Submitting this form is not necessary for entry or access into any area of the site.
Spacesaver collects and maintains all submitted information.
USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
All information collected or provided through this site will only be used by Spacesaver, its authorized Area Contractors, and others directly associated with Spacesaver. Only visitors providing Spacesaver with information via the “Download” or “Contact Us” forms will be contacted.
Disclosure
Spacesaver may disclose any information, without notice, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Spacesaver or this site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Spacesaver and its sites; and/or (c) protect the personal safety of customers of Spacesaver or the public.
CONSENT
How does Spacesaver get my consent?
When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, you are deemed to have consented to our collection and retention of the information provided, use of the information in order to perform the task you requested and disclosure of such information to third parties Spacesaver reasonably determines necessary in order to perform the requested task.
Unless you ask us not to, we may also contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
How do I withdraw my consent?
You may withdraw your consent for us to contact you for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at any time, by written instruction sent to Spacesavermktg@spacesaver.com or by mail at: Spacesaver Corporation, 1450 Janesville Ave., Fort Atkinson, Wisconsin US 53538
SHOPIFY
Our store is hosted on Shopify Inc. They provide us with the online e-commerce platform that allows us to sell our products and services to you.
Your data is stored through Shopify’s data storage, databases and the general Shopify application. They store your data on a secure server behind a firewall.
Payment:
If you choose a direct payment gateway to complete your purchase, then Shopify stores your credit card data. It is encrypted through the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS). Your purchase transaction data is stored only if it is necessary to complete your purchase transaction. After that is complete, your purchase transaction information is deleted.
All direct payment gateways adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, Mastercard, American Express and Discover.
PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of credit card information by our store and its service providers.
For more information, you may also read Shopify’s Terms of Service (https://www.shopify.com/legal/terms) or its Privacy Statement (https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy).
THIRD-PARTY SERVICES
In general, third-party service providers we use will only collect, use or disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.
However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions.
For these providers, we recommend you read their privacy policies so you can understand the way your personal information will be handled by these providers.
Remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities located a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So, if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.
As an example, if you are in Canada and your transaction is processed by a payment gateway located in the United States, your personal information used in completing that transaction may be subject to disclosure under United States legislation, including the Patriot Act.
Once you leave our store’s website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms of Service.
Links
When you click on links on our store, they may direct you away from our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements
SECURITY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
To protect your personal information, Spacesaver takes reasonable precautions and follows industry best practices to make sure your information is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.  Notwithstanding, Spacesaver cannot and does not guarantee the safety or privacy of your personal information, whether submitted to Spacesaver or collected via the mechanisms described in this Privacy Policy.
If you provide us with your credit card information, the information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and stored with a AES-256 encryption.  Although no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage is 100% secure, we follow all PCI-DSS requirements and implement additional generally accepted industry standards.
CHANGES TO THIS POLICY
Spacesaver will occasionally update this Privacy Policy. The “last updated” date at the top of this Privacy Policy will change to reflect such updates. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will apply to data collected after such changes have been made.
Spacesaver reserves the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website with the “last updated” date at the top of the page.
CONTACT INFORMATION
Question or Comments regarding this Privacy Policy can be directed to Spacesavermktg@spacesaver.com or by mail to Spacesaver Corporation, 1450 Janesville Avenue, Fort Atkinson, Wisconsin 53538 USA
PRODUCTS
High-Density Mobile Shelving
Evidence Storage
Filing Cabinet Storage
Locker Storage
Metal Shelving
Modular Storage
Museum Storage Products
Spacesaver Corporation 1450 Janesville Ave.Fort Atkinson, WI 53538
info@spacesaver.com
© 2020 Copyright Spacesaver Corporation. All Rights Reserved.
Terms
Legal Notice
Privacy Policy
Sitemap
